appolicious.com 2016-04-03

# Privacy Policy | Appolicious ™ iPhone and iPad App Directory

## Privacy Policy

Appolicious Inc. (“us” or “we”) is committed to protecting your online privacy.  This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for the www.appolicious.com website (our “Site”). We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully to learn what information we collect from you and how we use that information.

**1\. Information We Collect**

            We collect two types of information about users:  personally identifiable information (“personal information”), and non-personally identifiable information (“non-personal information”). 

**             **Personal information is information that identifies a specific user.  When you engage in certain activities that we make available on our Site, such as opening an account, submitting or posting content, or entering a contest, we may ask you to provide certain personal information, such as your name and email address.  While you can chose whether to engage in any such activity, if you do not provide required information, you will not be allowed to engage in that activity.

Non-personal information is information that does not identify a specific user.  This type of information may include things like the Uniform Resource Locator (“URL”) of the websites you visited before and after coming to our Site and your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address.  We and our authorized third-party service providers and ad servers may automatically collect this information when you visit our Site, as described in more detail below.    

**2\. How We Use the Information We Collect**

We use the information we collect in the following ways:For purposes for which you provided the information, such as to send you emails that you have requested;

  * To send you email notifications about our products and services and special offers;
  * To enhance the operation of our Site and allow us to personalize content and advertising;
  * To troubleshoot and accomplish other administrative tasks;
  * To analyze our user base and usage trends; and 
  * To enforce our Site Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy, comply with applicable law, and cooperate with law enforcement activities. 

**3\. Sharing of Your Personal Information**  

Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your personal information with other parties unless you opt-in to having your information shared with a party that is not affiliated with us. 

  * **We may share your information with Third-Party Service Providers _._** __  We may provide some of our services and products through third parties.  These third-party service providers perform functions on our behalf, like sending out our administrative and promotional emails or providing customer service.  We may share personal or non-personal information with such service providers to send emails, administer contests you enter, provide customer service, and troubleshoot.  In the case of personal information, the service providers will have access to your personal information solely for the purposes of providing such limited functions to us or on our behalf. 

  * **We may share your information in a** **Business Transfer**.  As with any other business, we could merge with or be acquired by another company.  If this occurs, the successor company would acquire the information we maintain, including both personal and non-personal information.  However, all of your information would remain subject to this Privacy Policy.

  * **We may share your information for o** **ur Protection and the Protection of Others.**   We may share personal and non-personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce this Privacy Policy, our Site Terms and Conditions or other agreements; or protect the rights, property or safety of our Site, its users or others.

**4 Cookies and Other Tracking Devices** **    **

To facilitate and customize your experience with our Site, we may place cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer that stores non-personal information about that user. We use cookies to save you time while using our Site and remind us who you are.  Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you may be able to modify your browser settings to decline or delete cookies.  Please note that if you decline or delete these cookies, some parts of our Site may not work properly.     ****

We may use a third-party analytic company to track and analyze non-personal usage information. In addition, we may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Site. These companies may place cookies on your computer in order to deliver targeted advertisements.  If you would like to opt-out of such collection by our third-party analytic contractor, please visit: <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>.  If you would like to opt-out of such collection by third-party advertising servers that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative, please visit:  <http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp>. 

Third-Party Web Beacons: We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Yahoo!, [click here.](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/opt_out/targeting/details.html)

We may use other industry-standard technologies like pixel tags and other web beacons to track your use of our Site.  Pixel tags and web beacons are tiny graphic images placed on certain pages on our Site or in our emails that allow us to determine whether you have performed a specific action. When you access these pages or open or click an email, pixel tags and web beacons generate a non-personally identifiable notice of that action.  Pixel tags allow us to measure user volume and behavior, and permit us to measure the performance of our promotions.   

**5\. Updating and Correcting Information**

            We encourage you to promptly update your personal information if it changes.  To access and edit your personal information, you may update your account at <http://appolicious.com/session/new> or contact us at legal@apolicious.com.

**6\. User Choices**

You can let us know that you do not wish to receive promotional emails from us when you open an account with us.  In addition, you can opt-out of promotional emails at any time after you open an account by:  (1) adjusting your account privacy preferences at <http://appolicious.com/session/new>; or (2) hitting the “unsubscribe” button at the bottom of any of these emails. 

**7\. Security of Personal Information**

            We take security seriously and take numerous precautions to protect the security of your personal information.  Your personal information resides on a secure server that only selected personnel and contractors have access to.  We encrypt certain sensitive information using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to ensure that your personal information is safe as it is transmitted to us.   

            Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  As a result, while we employ commercially reasonable security measures to protect data and seek to partner with companies which do the same, we cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted to or from our Site, and are not responsible for the actions of any third parties that may receive any such information.

**8\. Links to Other Sites**

            We may make content or services from other sites available to you from links located on our Site.  These other sites are not subject to this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you review the privacy policy at each such site to determine how that site protects your privacy. 

**9\. Miscellaneous Privacy Issues**

**             Children.  **Minors under the age of 13 may not use our Site.  We do not collect or maintain information from anyone known to be under the age of 13, and no part of our Site is designed to attract anyone under the age of 13.

**             Public Areas**.  If you disclose personal information in any discussion forums or other public areas on our Site, that information can be read, collected or used by others to send you unsolicited messages or for other purposes.  This Privacy Policy does not apply to such information.  If you do not want your comments to be viewed by third parties, do not make any such submissions.

**             Notice of Privacy Rights to California Residents**.  California law requires that we provide you with a summary of your privacy rights under the California Online Privacy Protection Act (the “Act”) and the California Business and Professions Code.  As required by the Act, we will provide you with the categories of personal information that we collect through our Site and the categories of third-party persons or entities with whom such personal information may be shared for direct marketing purposes at your request.   California law requires us to inform you, at your request:  (1) the categories of personal information we collect and what third parties we share that information with; (2) the names and addresses of those third parties; (3) examples of the products marketed by those companies.  California law further requires us to allow you to control who you do not want us to share the foregoing information with.  To obtain this information, please send a request by email or standard mail at the address found below.  When contacting us, please indicate your name, address, email address, and what personal information you do not want us to share.  The request should be sent to the attention of our legal department, and labeled “California Customer Choice Notice.”  Please allow 30 days for a response.  Also, please note that there is no charge for controlling the sharing of your personal information or requesting this notice. 

**10\. Changes to Privacy Policy**

            We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting the revised Privacy Policy in the “Privacy Policy” section of our Site.  You acknowledge that it is your responsibility to review our Site and the Privacy Policy periodically to learn of any modifications.  Your continued use of our Site after the posting of the revised Privacy Policy shall constitute your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy.    

11.  **Contacting Us**

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via email at legal@appolicious.com **** or in writing at Appolicious Inc., 225 West Washington Street, Suite 1500, Chicago, Illinois 60606.
